My loves, welcome. Thank you for your company.
Let's go for another episode of Ricon Moto GP's career mode.
We've already received offers to join other teams,
particularly within the Moto3 series.
And today we're at our sixth race.
Let's go to the Czech Republic Let'Grand s do as Prix.
always, Let'start s with go. that first day to figure out how the track works.
As soon as we do two or three laps around the track,
we'll already Let's go understand to qualifying how it and works.
then to the race to see what happens.
In episode two, it looks like we're going to end up doing something different, man.
If I'm not mistaken, motocross Well, or something it looks like like we'that.
re going to have rain, I don't know why.
I suspect we're going to have Variable rain this weekend.
climate. It will It might be? rain during training.
Come on, follow along. Okay, I'm going to go out here with soft rear tires and
medium front tires. Come on, let's go to the track and try to figure[out Clearing
what the throat]track Come is like.
on, let's go and see how Ricon is going to get away with it.
Now the other teams are right behind us, because we've managed to get some pretty
good scores, have n't we?
Wow, you have to take this corner really fast because of the finish line straight,
right?
You've already left here, haven't you?
Okay. This track is going to be fast, it hurts, man.
This track is going to be so fast, man.
It's
going to be quick this time. Please don't bring rain here to this damn place,
or we'll be stuck. AND.
Hold that
accelerator for me, Ricardo.
Here's a section that's more complex, although it has some very fast parts.
There are some really creepy curves here, aren't there?
And this track has brutal curves.
It had to be, right? It had to be.
You're tired of fueling yourself up and saying,"Ricardo, watch the accelerator.
Watch the accelerator. What are you going to do?
I'm going to have a bad time on this corner.
I don't know why, but I'm suspicious.
bad time. I'm going And to look have at a this, look at this mountain.
Look at this mountain.
Yeah, we have to exit really well onto this finish straight, right?
That wasn't bad. That wasn't bad.
This is it. If we mess up, forget it.
We lost a ton of speed, man.
28. We still do. They still don't have time, right?
This track is going to be monstrous.
This track is going to be monstrous, man, for me to stay here in the front
positions.
And here it's just a matter of letting go.
It has to be letting go at the right moment, man.
27. Nice.
It doesn't lift.
You're struggling to lift it.
Well, let's go back to the pits.
I think we have a good time.[snoring]Well, let's finish,
close the practice session and let's go Let's see what happens.
Zés rev campers. Res campers.
This is going to be a close race.
I'm telling you now. It's not going to be easy.
Don't think it's going to be easy, that we'll just get here and put a huge time on
the guys. It's not going to be easy especially at all.
It was if just it practice, rains.
I was already expecting this.
Oh, damn. I'm going to have a really Oh, the hard rain, time guys.
in the rain. Well, what is it?
Let's go, let's go. Let's go to the track.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let'Let's see s go, if this let'one s holds go.
up for now. So cold it hurts, right?
For now, the tires are really cold.
And the bike is very cornering, much less so.
OK, let's try to warm up the tires first right?
I
think the first, the only times we raced in the rain, I wasn't using rain tires.
I wasn't using Rain tires. Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
We're going to have to be very careful with the throttle in the rain, guys.
It's going to
be beautiful. It will, it will, it will.
It's going to be beautiful. It will, it will.
It's going to be
very beautiful, guys. It's going to be very beautiful.
It will, it will. Increase the TCS.
Otherwise I'm stuck. And I think I will.
Oh, my teammate didn't even notice.
I didn't even
notice it was my teammate.
It's
going to be tough. Very tough.
Very tough, guys. Very tough.
It's going to be very tough.
Now it came too early, didn't it?
Well, it wasn't too early. Did we already do a lap or not?
Ah, no, because you went off, right?
The time was invalid, right?
Damn, you have to brake earlier, Ricardo.
You have to brake earlier, otherwise it won't work.
We'll brake earlier, otherwise it won't work, man.
We'll brake slightly earlier.
I prefer to be slower, but win.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, Oh, oh.
Even braking earlier, man.
Look at this, man.
Even braking earlier.
Damn, I have to brake way earlier, man.
Way earlier.
Look at this. Just him slowing down on his own, I wasn't even braking anymore.
It was just him slowing down, man.
It's
going to be really hard to keep up with these guys.
I think I'll improve a little here, or not?
Rain is really not my thing. Look at that.
Rain is really not my thing, guys.
Let's start from down here
. Fog, if I'm braking, it's before, man.
That's it. It's confusing me.
It was yellow. Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh.
Wiping the guy's legs, man.
Damn man. Could it be that I don't have the right tires?
No, the tires, the rain tires, it's just rain tires.
There are no medium ones here, Neither soft nor hard, right?
We just
can't get a lap. The thing is, I need to get a lap.
The thing is, I need to get a lap, guys.
18th place, man. Look,
did you see her escaping? She's always escaping.
I have the TCS on C, Zé, let's get a lap.
I'm just stuck guys.
Yeah, the thing is to brake well before, man.
The thing is to brake well before.
Did you see how much time we've already gained?
Look there
. Even so, damn,
even so, look at the time I lost here.
You have to
be extra careful in the rain, man, brutal.
The gameplay changes completely.
Oh, if I accelerate there, I'm going down.
If I accelerate there, I'm going down, guys.
I improved a little, but I don't know if it's enough for the top 10.
I
don't know if it's enough for the top 10.
I'll tell you now. Hold on,
devil's bike.
We're taking off 3 and a half seconds.
And I could have accelerated full throttle, man.
I was Okay. Well, we're going to shave off a lot of time, guys.
Practically three and a half seconds.
Oh, old man. We did the lap, guys, the lap with adaptation.
Did you see? That's it, that's the progression that's in the adaptation that
exists this year, which didn't exist in other years, man.
I think Very it's good,[clearing very throat]good.
But very as good, you saw, man. I didn't get close to the guy in front.
Even so, he must have stayed just a few seconds below me.
Very good, man. Very good. Do you think we'll pass?
Let's see. Hey, guys, we're taking off, Three, we'three re taking tenths, right?
off a We'few re tenths. taking off three tenths.
Look there. Look there. It's a little better.
It's a little better. But I think it's going to rain in the race.
I think it's going to rain, guys.
I think it's going to end up we raining adapt here.
in the Let'race. s see Come what on, tires let's it see is.
how Okay, let's go. I think the tires are good, right?
So, let's go. Listen to these screams, these screams.
Oh, no. Let's go to the race already.
Let's go Okay, to the let'race s already, go.
man. I didn't even realize it was the race already.
Look at that. Let's go, let's see what this is going to lead to.
I didn't even realize it was the race already, man.
That this was the race already.
Our bike doesn't have a very good start, does it?
You
messed up here. Let's go.
It's
going to be tough to catch up with those guys already.
Okay.
Yeah.
Careful, Ricardo. I messed up here.
I messed up here. It hurts so badly.
I know it hurts so badly. Here.
Here, it hurts so badly, guys.
I know it hurts so
badly again. And this is the most important race we have,
guys.
Hey Ricardo.
Damn, man.
I
braked too late. I felt I braked too late.
Let's go, let's go, let's try for the podium, guys.
Let's go.
Those two are going to take the...
Middle of the gallows.
Those two
This guy's anxious.
Hold on. Let's go.
Do we have to increase the TCS a little or what?
It's tough to catch these two guys.
Let's go
. You did very well.
You did very well Ricardo.
Except the guys have motorcycles.
Ah Ricardo too early, man.
But anyway, we got closer to the guys, right?
What a beautiful race, Zé.
What a beautiful race, man.
Oh.
What a beautiful race, old man.
Ah,
tell Tak.
[cough]What a race is this?
What a race was this, guys.
What a race was this until I took the lead.
The guys started to fall behind, what?
Tire or what?
Damn, the guys braked much later than me.
They braked much later than me.
This is still undecided.
This speed, this adaptive difficulty is very good in the
game, guys. This adaptive speed is very good in the game,
guys.
You don't
have to look at Back, Barbidelis.
This shit's gonna be a fight to the finish.
(Free users can only transcribe the first 30 minutes. Upgrade to re-transcribe the full file.)
(Transcribed by UniScribe (https://www.uniscribe.co). Upgrade to remove this message.)